CNN has decided not to run a
Donald Trump endorsed campaign
ad after the network decided it
does not meet their standards.
The 32nd advertisement paid for
by Trump's campaign targeted Joe
Biden's conduct toward Ukraine
while he served as vice president,
while also referring to CNN
personalities Don lemon, Chris Cuomo
and Jim Acosta as media lapdogs.
A CNN spokesperson spoke to
saying the ad does not meet the
network's advertising standards,
adding in addition to disparaging
CNN and its journalists,
the ad makes assertions that have
been proven demonstrably false by
various news outlets, including CNN.
However, despite CNN's rejection,
the president posted the
advertisement onto his Twitter page
last week along with the caption
I'm draining the swamp now.
This is not the first time CNN
has rejected a Trump campaign ad.
Back in 2017, the network refused
to run a Trump approved ad called
Let President Trump Do His Job,
which criticized the media and
specifically called out lemon,
as well as Anderson Cooper, to stay
up to date on the story. Hit the.com.
And until next time for The Hollywood
Reporter. News and media joins.