I think if you're a leader and
you don't understand the terms
that you're using,
that's probably the first start.
It's really important that as, uh,
a leader in the organization, you
understand what digitization means.
You take the time to read widely
in the sector.
There are a lot of really good books.
Kevin Kelly, who started Wide
Magazine, has written a great,
uh, great book on, uh,
on various technologies.
I think understanding the
technologies, understanding
what's out there so that you can
separate the hype from the hope is
really an important first step,
and then making sure you understand
the relevance of that for your
function and how that fits into
your business is the second.
Step, I think, to two simple,
uh, suggestions.
You know, one one is I love the
phrase brilliant at the basics.
Right.
So, you know, how can you become
brilliant at the basics?
But beyond that, um, you know,
the fundamental thing I've seen
which hasn't changed is so few
organizations, as a first step,
have truly taken control of their
spend data, you know, as a key first
step on a digital transformation,
taking ownership of data.
And that's not a decision to use
one vendor over someone else
that says we are going to be
completely data driven.
We're going to try and be as
real time as possible.
And we're we're going to be able
to explain that data to anyone
the way they want to see it.
Understand why you're doing it.
And then the second thing is reach
out to suppliers in the market,
talk to them, collaborate with them.
You'll get a much better outcome.
Think about what outcome you want
at the end instead of thinking
about the different processes
and the software names.
So e sourcing being one of 20,
think big and be brave.
I think um, and talk to technology
vendors because rather than just
sending them forms we won't bite.
You know I think we should
fundamentally all of us rethink
how procurement should be done
and then start to define the
functionality that we need and
how we can make this work. Yeah.
What we're doing today is
absolutely well, we don't like it.
Procurement people don't like it.
Our colleagues don't like it.
Nobody wants it. Yeah.
And we spending a huge amount of
money for no reason.